English Department. Records. 1969-1983.
UCLA Library Special Collections
English Department. Records.
1969-1983
University Archives Record Series 641
UCLA Library Special Collections
0.4 linear ft. (1 box)
Record Series 641 contains records generated by the Department of English at the University of California, Los Angeles between 1969 and 1983.
University of California, Los Angeles. Department of English.
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Portions of Record Series 641 are restricted and not open for research. See folder descriptions for more information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 641 contains records generated by the Department of English at the University of California, Los Angeles between 1969 and 1983. Files regard the Composition Section, personnel, budgets, and other operations of the department.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3466850
- Promotion: rosters and notices., 1974-1982. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Composition: relations with schools., 1979-1980. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Composition Section (CS): guidelines., 1980. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Composition Section (CS): budget., 1980-1981. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Composition Section (CS): general., 1980-1982. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Composition Section (CS): staffing., 1981-1982. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Composition Section (CS): general., 1982-1983. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Composition Section (CS): reappointments and appointments., 1982-1983. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Recruitment: minority faculty., 1969-1973. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Folder 9 is restricted and not open for research until 2053.
- TA questionnaires and complaints., 1978 Spring. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Folder 10 is restricted and not open for research until 2058.